minimob.com 2014-02-08

# Privacy Policy | Minimob - Mobile Advertising

This Privacy Policy ("Policy") explains how your personal information is collected, used and disclosed by Minimob, Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates ("Minimob"). This Policy applies to Minimob's website, located at [www.minimob.com](http://www.minimob.com/) ("Site") as well as Minimob's mobile advertising platform, technology, features, products and services ("Service").

Minimob may change this Policy from time to time. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the "Last Updated" date above. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact Minimob at [support@minimob.com](mailto:support@minimob.com).

## Our service

### Data Collected through Our Service

Minimob's Service enables mobile application developers to provide free, ad-supported applications to end users. When you download a mobile application that utilizes our Service, we may collect information from your mobile device in accordance with the permissions you have granted when installing the application. For example, in accordance with the permissions you have granted, we may collect your device ID, device make and model, device IP address, mobile web browser type and version, mobile carrier, real-time location information, email address, phone number and a list of the mobile applications on your device.

### Use of Data We Collect through Our Service

We may use personal information collected through our Service for the purposes described in this Policy, including to:

  * operate and improve our Service;
  * monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Service; and
  * deliver personalized advertisements to your mobile device.

We may store and process the information we collect through our Service in the EU.

### Disclosure of Data Collected through Our Service

We may share personal information about you as follows:

  * with third party advertisers who are a part of the Minimob mobile advertising platform for their direct marketing purposes;
  * with third party vendors, consultants and other service providers who work on our behalf or with us to provide our Service and need access to your information to carry out their work for us;
  * to (i) comply with laws or to respond to lawful requests and legal process, (ii) to protect the rights and property of Minimob our agents, customers, members, and others including to enforce our agreements, policies and terms of use or (iii) in an emergency to protect the safety of Minimob, its customers or any person; 
  * in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of Minimob assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company; and
  * with your consent, including if we notify you on the Service that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information.

We may also share aggregated or de-identified information with third parties

### Your Information Choices Regarding Our Service

When you download a mobile application from an application developer that is part of our mobile advertising platform, we may begin to collect data from your mobile device and you may receive advertisements on your mobile device. We provide notice of our collection, use and disclosure of your information when you install a mobile application that contains our Service. At any time, you may delete the application that contains our Service, which will prevent us from collecting any information from your mobile device and prevent the delivery of advertisements to your mobile device.

Please see the instructions below for additional information on how you can manage your preferences regarding the delivery of our advertisements.

**Push Notification Ads:** Push Notification Ads are placed in your notification tray alongside other notifications. Each notification advertisement is tagged with the name of the mobile application that is responsible for enabling the advertisement to be delivered to your mobile device as well as a link to our opt-out site, located at http://dashboard.minimob.com/opt-out.asp ("Opt-Out Site"). The Opt-Out Site provides you with two methods to prevent future notification ads from being delivered to your mobile device. First, users can permanently opt-out of receiving any future notification ads from Minimob by installing and running our opt-out application. Second, users can manually enter their IMEI number into our Opt-Out Site to see the individual applications installed on their device that are a part of our mobile advertising platform. Users can then individually delete these applications if they would like to stop receiving our advertisements. Please note, if you choose to manually delete applications rather than install our opt-out application, you may begin to receive our advertisements in the future if you download an application that is part of our mobile advertising platform.

**Icon Ads:** Icon Ads may appear on the home screen of your mobile device. Users can delete Icon Ads with one click. Alternatively, users may follow the opt-out process outlined in the Push Notification Ads section above to prevent future Icon Ads from appearing.

**In-App Ads:** Signup Ads, and certain other forms of in-app advertisements, may be displayed within your mobile applications. Users can click the 'Skip' button to bypass a Signup Ad and proceed to the main app activity. Other in-app advertisements may be ignored or the user can close the application to prevent viewing these advertisements.

### Security of Your Data

Minimob takes reasonable precautions to safeguard the personal information we collect through our Service in an effort to prevent loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

## Our site

### Data Collected through Our Site

We collect information about you in various ways when you use our Site. For example, we collect personal information you provide to us when you register for a developer or advertiser account, use the interactive areas and features of our Site and when you email, call or otherwise communicate with us. The types of information we collect may include your name, email address, phone number, billing address, social security number, tax identification number, bank account information and other contact or demographic information.

When you visit our Site, some information is automatically collected. For example, when you visit our Site your operating system, IP address, access times, browser type and language, and the website you visited before our Site are logged automatically. We also collect information about your usage and activity on our Site.

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies:** We use cookies and other technologies on our Site to see which areas and features are popular and to count visits to our Site. Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Site.

We may also receive personal information about you from other sources, including third parties in accordance with their respective privacy policies. We may associate this information with the other personal information we have collected about you.

### Use of Data Collected through Our Site

We use personal information collected through our Site for purposes described in this Policy or otherwise disclosed to you in connection with our Site. For example, we may use your personal information to:

  * operate and improve the Site,
  * respond to your comments and questions and provide customer service;
  * monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Site,
  * provide and deliver your products and services and to send you related information, including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
  * communicate with you about new contests, promotions and rewards, upcoming events, and other news about products and services offered by Minimob and our selected partners; and
  * link or combine with other personal information we get from third parties, to help understand your needs and provide you with better service.

We may store and process personal information in the European Union and elsewhere.

### Disclosure of Data Collected through Our Site

We do not share the personal information collected through our Site with third parties other than as follows:

  * with third party vendors, consultants and other service providers who work on our behalf or with us to provide the Site, and need access to your information to carry out their work;
  * to (i) comply with laws or to respond to lawful requests and legal process, (ii) to protect the rights and property of Minimob our agents, customers, members, and others including to enforce our agreements, policies and terms of use or (iii) in an emergency to protect the safety of Minimob, its customers or any person; and
  * in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of Minimob assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company;
  * with your consent, including if we notify you that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information;

We may also share aggregated or anonymized information with third parties.

### Your Information Choices Regarding Our Site

You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from Minimob by following the instructions in those emails. You may also send requests about your contact preferences and changes to your information by emailing [support@minimob.com](mailto:support@minimob.com). If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your accounts or our ongoing business relations.

### Security of Your Data

Minimob takes measures to safeguard your personal information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.
